thekidshouldseethis.com 2019-04-24

# Privacy Policy | The Kid Should See This

_Updated November 9, 2017_

The Kid Should See This™ (“TKSST” or “We”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes the treatment of information We collect from and about you when you visit our website or use our services that contain a link to this Privacy Policy or otherwise refer to or provide the URL to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Services”). Our Privacy Policy also describes other sources we use to obtain information about you; tells you how We use, share and protect your information; and what choices you have about how your information is used.

All content, products and services are intended for general audiences and are NOT directed to children. We do not knowingly permit children under age 13 to register for any content, product or Service. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. If We learn We have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of consent from a parent or guardian, We will delete that information. If you believe We might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at thekidshouldseethis{at}gmail.com.

**Collection of Information**

**Information You Provide Directly**  
If you are interested in obtaining information, products or services from TKSST™, or participating in certain activities through the Services, you may need to provide us or our service providers with information about yourself. For example:

  * If you register for a Service to receive a newsletter, or get information about TKSST™ promotions or events, you may be asked for your email address.

**Information We May Collect Automatically**  
In addition to information you choose to provide to us, TKSST™ and our service providers also use standard technologies to automatically collect certain additional information. For example:

  * **IP Address and Other Identifiers.** When you access and interact with our Services, TKSST™ and our service providers may collect information about your visits in order to permit you to connect to and obtain the Services and to understand the frequency with which specific visitors visit various parts of our Services. For example, We may collect your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, which identifies the computer or service provider that you use to access the Services, or information about your browser type, authentication identifiers, and other software and hardware information. If you access the Services through a mobile or other device We may collect your mobile device identifier, geolocation data (including your precise location), or other transactional information for that device. We may combine this information with other information that We have collected to make our Services and our communications to you more targeted to your interests.
  * **Social Media Information and Content.** If you access or log into a Service through a social media service or connect a Service to a social media service, the information We collect may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with that social media service, any information or content you have permitted the social media service to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends lists, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. When you access the Services through social media services or when you connect a Service to social media services, you are authorizing TKSST™ to collect, store, and use such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
  * **Cookies.** Our Services may also use cookies. Cookies are small text files that are stored on a user’s computer and allow websites to remember information about users. We and our service providers use cookies for a variety of purposes in order to enhance the quality of our sites.
  * **Web beacons and other tracking technologies.** The Services may use other tracking tools, including so-called “pixel tags,” “web beacons,” “web bugs,” “clear GIFs,”etc. (collectively “Web Beacons”) to collect user activity information about your activities on the Services. These are small electronic images embedded in web content (including online ads) and email messages and are ordinarily not visible to users. Like cookies, Web Beacons enable us to track pages and content (including ads) accessed and viewed by users. Also, when We send HTML-formatted (as opposed to plain text) emails to you, Web Beacons may be embedded in such emails to allow us to monitor readership levels so that We can identify aggregate trends and individual usage to provide our audiences with more relevant content or offers. Web Beacons in emails may recognize activities such as when an email was opened, how many times an email was forwarded, which links in the email were clicked on, etc. Web Beacons cannot be declined when delivered via a regular web page. However, Web Beacons can be refused when delivered via email. If you do not wish to receive Web Beacons via email, you will need to disable HTML images or refuse HTML (select Text only) emails via your email software.

**Information from Other Sources**  
TKSST™ and our service providers may supplement the information We collect from and about you with information from other sources, such as publicly available information from social media services.

**Third-Party Online Advertising**  
Some of the advertisements you see on the Services are delivered by third parties who also collect information through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies that collect information about your online activities on this and other websites in an effort to deliver advertisements that are tailored to your interests. These third parties also may use information about you that We provide, such as your email address, or the features within the Services that you use to target and serve advertisements to you and to analyze the delivery of advertisements on the Services. However, We will not provide personal information about you to these companies, except as permitted under this Privacy Policy.

Third parties may serve ads on our Services, and thereby may collect information about your online activities to deliver tailored ads. These companies may offer you a way to choose not to have your information used for advertising purposes. These and other third-party companies may also be members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”), which offers a single location to opt out of receiving tailored ads from member companies. To opt out or to obtain information about the technologies member companies use or their own privacy policies, please visit the NAI consumer opt out page. Also, through the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”), several media and marketing associations have developed an industry self-regulatory program to give consumers a better understanding of and greater control over ads that are customized based on their online behavior across different desktop and mobile web browsers and apps. To make choices about interest-based ads from participating third parties, please visit the DAA consumer opt out page.

**Use and Disclosure**

TKSST™ and our service providers may use information that We collect from and about you for a variety of business purposes, including:

  * to deliver content and services that you request, and enhance your experience on our Services;
  * to process and track your activity on the website and provide the Services and content you request;
  * to communicate with you about the content and Services or other products, content or services in which you may be interested, or to respond to your inquiries or comments;
  * to deliver advertising;
  * to perform business analyses or for other purposes to improve the quality of our business, the Services, and the products and services We offer; or
  * in accordance with your consent.

In order to curate our content, Services and advertising more interesting and relevant to you, We may use the information We collect from and about you to make inferences and predictions about your potential areas of interest. When the information collected from or about you does not identify you as a specific person, We may use that information for any purpose or share it with third parties, to the extent permitted by applicable law.

We will use and share personal information as described in this Privacy Policy, including:

  * With entities that help us to manage and provide the Services, including development of our website, maintenance and support, personalization, email distribution, measurement and improvement, only to the extent that these entities need the information to perform their services or as required by law;
  * In response to legal process and when We believe that doing so is required by law, may be necessary to protect any person’s property, rights, or safety, or to investigate a potential violation of law, will help to enforce any terms of use or other legal agreement, or in the event of a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, bankruptcy or asset sale;
  * In accordance with your consent.

When information We collect is aggregated, anonymized or otherwise does not identify you, We may use that information for any purpose or share it with third parties, to the extent permitted by applicable law.

**User Access and Control**

You may opt out of having your personal information used or disclosed for certain purposes.

  * If you no longer want to receive marketing-related emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out of receiving these emails be clicking “Unsubscribe” or “Update my Preferences” at the bottom of any marketing email you receive.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If We do, We will let you know by revising the date at the top of the policy.

**Do Not Track Signals**

California Law requires us to disclose how We respond to “Do Not Track” signals. At this time, We do not respond to browser ‘Do Not Track’ signals, as We await the work of interested stakeholders and others to develop standards for how such signals should be interpreted.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please email thekidshouldseethis{at}gmail.com.
